Henry Y. Porter Theater Memorabilia Collection MS003
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Artists and other celebrities; prints, photographs, and artifacts, 1722 -- 1990; 1880 -- 1920; MS003.001; 33.95 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes; 4 Digital Object(s)
  - Singers, 8x10, baritones and basses, all signed, 1890 -- 1961; MS003.001.031
    - Herbert Janssen (1895-1965), German baritone, 1941; MS003.001.031.00065 (Box 31)
    - Arthur Kent (1906-1980), American baritone, 1941; MS003.001.031.00066 (Box 31)
    - Frederick Lechner (1904-1984), German baritone, 1944; MS003.001.031.00067 (Box 31)
    - George London (1920-1985), Canadian baritone, 1953; MS003.001.031.00068 (Box 31)
    - Carlo Morelli (1898-1970), Italian baritone, 1936; MS003.001.031.00069 (Box 31)
    - Hans Hermann Nissen (1896-1980), German baritone, 1939; MS003.001.031.00070 (Box 31)
    - Hans Hermann Nissen (1896-1980), German baritone, 1939; MS003.001.031.00071 (Box 31)
    - Walter Loitzki (1903-1949), German baritone, 1940; MS003.001.031.00072 (Box 31)
    - Taurun Parus, baritone, 1920; MS003.001.031.00073 (Box 31)
    - Fred Patton (1888-1951), American baritone, 1937; MS003.001.031.00074 (Box 31)
    - Giacomo Rimini (1880-1955), Italian baritone, 1930; MS003.001.031.00075 (Box 31)
    - Horner Rodeheaver (1880-1955), American baritone, 1925; MS003.001.031.00076 (Box 31)
    - Paul Robeson (1898-1976), American baritone, 1930; MS003.001.031.00077 (Box 31)
    - Joseph Royer (1884-1965), American baritone, 1920; MS003.001.031.00078 (Box 31)
    - Sir Charles Stanley (1834-1922), English baritone, 1890; MS003.001.031.00079 (Box 31)
    - Titta Ruffo (1887-1953), Italian baritone, 1912, 1925 (2 photographs), MS003.001.031.00080 (Box 31)
    - Friedrich Schon (1888-1953), Hungarian baritone, 1935; MS003.001.031.00081 (Box 31)
    - Antonio Scotti (1866-1936), Italian baritone, 1922, 1926 (2 photographs), MS003.001.031.00082 (Box 31)
    - Edgar Schofield (1889-1966), American baritone, 1926; MS003.001.031.00083 (Box 31)
    - Gustave Schutzendorf (1883-1937), German baritone, 1936; MS003.001.031.00084 (Box 31)
    - Joseph Schwartz (1880-1926), Austrian baritone, 1925; MS003.001.031.00085 (Box 31)
    - Riccardo Stracciari (1875-1955), Italian baritone, (2 photographs), 1910 -- 1927; MS003.001.031.00086 (Box 31)
    - Oscar Seagle (1877-1945), American baritone, 1910; MS003.001.031.00087 (Box 31)
    - Alexander Sved (1906-1979), Hungarian baritone, 1944; MS003.001.031.00088 (Box 31)
    - Carlo Tagliabue (1898-1978), Italian baritone, 1940; MS003.001.031.00089 (Box 31)
    - John Charles Thomas (1891-1960), American baritone, 1920; MS003.001.031.00090 (Box 31)
    - John Charles Thomas (1891-1960), American baritone, 1950; MS003.001.031.00091 (Box 31)
    - Lawrence Tibbet (1896-1960), American baritone, 1940; MS003.001.031.00092 (Box 31)
    - Lawrence Tibbet (1896-1960), American baritone, 1920; MS003.001.031.00093 (Box 31)
    - Hermann Uhde (1914-1965), German baritone, 1961; MS003.001.031.00094 (Box 31)
    - Mario Valle (1882-1951), Italian baritone, 1940; MS003.001.031.00095 (Box 31)
    - Leonard Warren (1911-1960), American baritone, 1950; MS003.001.031.00096 (Box 31)
    - Robert Weede (1903-1972), American baritone, 1940; MS003.001.031.00097 (Box 31)
    - Reinald Weirenrath (1883-1953), American baritone, 1920; MS003.001.031.00098 (Box 31)
    - Clarence Whithall (1871-1932), American baritone, 1923; MS003.001.031.00099 (Box 31)
    - Clarence Whithall (1871-1932), American baritone (2 photographs), 1929 -- 1930; MS003.001.031.00100 (Box 31)
    - Renato Zanelli (1892-1935), Chilean baritone, 1930; MS003.001.031.00101 (Box 31)
  - Singers, 8x10, sopranos, all signed, 1880 -- 1960; MS003.001.032
    - Frances Alda (1883-1952), English soprano, 1923; MS003.001.032.00001 (Box 32)
    - Frances Alda (1883-1952), English soprano, 1935; MS003.001.032.00002 (Box 32)
    - Frances Alda (1883-1952), English soprano, 1925; MS003.001.032.00003 (Box 32)
    - Frances Alda (1883-1952), English soprano, 1920; MS003.001.032.00004 (Box 32)
    - Elsa Alsen (1892-1975), German soprano, 1936; MS003.001.032.00005 (Box 32)
    - Blanche Anal (1865-1945), Belgian soprano, 1900; MS003.001.032.00006 (Box 32)
    - Josephine Antoine (1907-1971), American soprano, 1935; MS003.001.032.00007 (Box 32)
    - Josephine Antoine (1907-1971), American soprano, 1950; MS003.001.032.00008 (Box 32)
    - Florence Austral (1894-1968), Australian soprano, 1920; MS003.001.032.00009 (Box 32)
    - Florence Austral (1894-1968), Australian soprano, 1945; MS003.001.032.00010 (Box 32)
    - Florence Austral (1894-1968), Australian soprano, 1950; MS003.001.032.00011 (Box 32)
    - Gladys Axman (1895-1968), American soprano, 1923; MS003.001.032.00012 (Box 32)
    - Maria Barrientos (1883-1946), Spanish soprano, 1930; MS003.001.032.00013 (Box 32)
    - Mimi Benzell (1924-1970), American soprano, 1950; MS003.001.032.00014 (Box 32)
    - Lucrezia Bori (1887-1960), Spanish soprano, 1920; MS003.001.032.00015 (Box 32)
    - Lucrezia Bori (1887-1960), Spanish soprano, 1938; MS003.001.032.00016 (Box 32)
    - Lucrezia Bori (1887-1960), Spanish soprano, 1930; MS003.001.032.00017 (Box 32)
    - Vina Bovy (1900-1983), Belgian soprano, 1937; MS003.001.032.00018 (Box 32)
    - Hilda Burke (1905-1978), American soprano, 1935; MS003.001.032.00019 (Box 32)
    - Emma Calvi (1858-1942), French soprano, 1923; MS003.001.032.00020 (Box 32)
    - Emma Calvi (1858-1942), French soprano, 1930; MS003.001.032.00021 (Box 32)
    - Mari Caniglia (1906-1979), Italian soprano, 1938; MS003.001.032.00022 (Box 32)
    - Mari Caniglia (1906-1979), Italian soprano, 1935; MS003.001.032.00023 (Box 32)
    - Toti Dal Monti (1898-1975), Italian soprano, 1934; MS003.001.032.00024 (Box 32)
    - Toti Dal Monti (1898-1975), Italian soprano, 1925; MS003.001.032.00025 (Box 32)
    - Toti Dal Monti (1898-1975), Italian soprano, 1925; MS003.001.032.00026 (Box 32)
    - Lina Cavalieri (1874-1944), Italian soprano, 1925; MS003.001.032.00027 (Box 32)
    - Emmy Destinn (1878-1930), Czech soprano, 1928; MS003.001.032.00028 (Box 32)
    - Doris Doree (1911-1971), American soprano, 1945; MS003.001.032.00029 (Box 32)
    - Claire Dux (1885-1967), German soprano, 1934; MS003.001.032.00030 (Box 32)
    - Florence Easton (1884-1955), English soprano, 1950; MS003.001.032.00031 (Box 32)
    - Florence Easton (1884-1955), English soprano, 1920; MS003.001.032.00032 (Box 32)
    - Geraldine Farrar (1882-1967), American soprano, 1923; MS003.001.032.00033 (Box 32)
    - Geraldine Farrar (1882-1967), American soprano, 1910; MS003.001.032.00034 (Box 32)
    - Geraldine Farrar (1882-1967), American soprano, 1960; MS003.001.032.00035 (Box 32)
    - Geraldine Farrar (1882-1967), American soprano, 1925; MS003.001.032.00036 (Box 32)
    - Kirstin Flagstead (1895-1962), Norwegian soprano, 1920; MS003.001.032.00037 (Box 32)
    - Kirstin Flagstead (1895-1962), Norwegian soprano, 1936; MS003.001.032.00038 (Box 32)
    - Kirstin Flagstead (1895-1962), Norwegian soprano, 1930; MS003.001.032.00039 (Box 32)
    - Bettina Freeman, American soprano, 1900; MS003.001.032.00040 (Box 32)
    - Olive Fremstad (1870-1951), American soprano, 1900; MS003.001.032.00041 (Box 32)
    - Olive Fremstad (1870-1951), American soprano, 1910; MS003.001.032.00042 (Box 32)
    - Olive Fremstad (1870-1951), American soprano, 1915; MS003.001.032.00043 (Box 32)
    - Olive Fremstad (1870-1951), American soprano, 1922; MS003.001.032.00044 (Box 32)
    - Johanna Gadski (1872-1932), German soprano, 1920; MS003.001.032.00045 (Box 32)
    - Amelita Galli-Curci (1882-1963), Italian soprano, 1919; MS003.001.032.00046 (Box 32)
    - Amelita Galli-Curci (1882-1963), Italian soprano, 1922; MS003.001.032.00047 (Box 32)
    - Amelita Galli-Curci (1882-1963), Italian soprano, 1916; MS003.001.032.00048 (Box 32)
    - The costumes of Amelita Galli-Curci, 1940; MS003.001.032.00049 (Box 32)
    - Mary Garden (1874-1967), Scotch soprano, 1924; MS003.001.032.00050 (Box 32)
    - Mary Garden (1874-1967), Scotch soprano, 1919; MS003.001.032.00051 (Box 32)
    - Lucy Gates, soprano, 1924; MS003.001.032.00052 (Box 32)
    - Alma Gluck, soprano, 1900 -- 1930; MS003.001.032.00053 (Box 32)
    - Margaret Halstead (1904-1970), American soprano, 1937; MS003.001.032.00054 (Box 32)
    - Frieda Hempel (1885-1955), German soprano, 1920; MS003.001.032.00055 (Box 32)
    - Frieda Hempel (1885-1955), German soprano, 1940; MS003.001.032.00056 (Box 32)
    - Frieda Hempel (1885-1955), German soprano, 1940; MS003.001.032.00057 (Box 32)
    - Edith Helena (1876-1956), American soprano, 1920; MS003.001.032.00058 (Box 32)
    - Edith Helena (1876-1956), American soprano, 1912; MS003.001.032.00059 (Box 32)
    - Maria Jeritza (1887-1982), Austrian soprano, 1930; MS003.001.032.00060 (Box 32)
    - Dorothy Jardon (1883-1966), American soprano, 1915; MS003.001.032.00061 (Box 32)
    - Gertrude Kappel (1884-1971), German soprano, 1925; MS003.001.032.00062 (Box 32)
    - Olive Kline (1885-1976), American soprano, 1923; MS003.001.032.00063 (Box 32)
    - Hilde Konetzui (1905-1980), Austrian soprano, 1934; MS003.001.032.00064 (Box 32)
    - Miliza Korjus (?-1930), American soprano, 1920 -- 1950; MS003.001.032.00065 (Box 32)
    - Maria Kurenko (1890-1980), Russian soprano, 1920; MS003.001.032.00066 (Box 32)
    - Melanie Kurt (19880-1941), Austrian soprano, 1910; MS003.001.032.00067 (Box 32)
    - Nanny Larsen-Todsen (1884-1982), Swedish soprano, 1925; MS003.001.032.00068 (Box 32)
    - Hilda Lashanska (1893-1974), American soprano, 1923; MS003.001.032.00069 (Box 32)
    - Marjorie Lawrence (1908-1979), Australian soprano, 1943; MS003.001.032.00070 (Box 32)
    - Marjorie Lawrence (1908-1979), Australian soprano, 1937; MS003.001.032.00071 (Box 32)
    - Georgette Le Blanc (1875-1941), French soprano, 1924; MS003.001.032.00072 (Box 32)
    - Lotte Lehmann (1888-1975), German soprano, 1936; MS003.001.032.00073 (Box 32)
    - Lotte Lehmann (1888-1975), German soprano, 1951; MS003.001.032.00074 (Box 32)
    - Frida Leider (1886-1975), German soprano, 1925; MS003.001.032.00075 (Box 32)
    - Lydia Sipkowska (1882-1955), Russian soprano, 1925; MS003.001.032.00076 (Box 32)
    - Gota Ljingberg (1893-1955), Swedish soprano, 1930; MS003.001.032.00077 (Box 32)
    - Felice Lyne (1891-1935), American soprano, 1920; MS003.001.032.00078 (Box 32)
    - Dorothea Manski (1891-1967), American soprano, 1937; MS003.001.032.00079 (Box 32)
    - Queena Mario (1896-1952), American soprano, 1930; MS003.001.032.00080 (Box 32)
    - Lucy Isabella Marsh (1878-1956), American soprano, 1920; MS003.001.032.00081 (Box 32)
    - Edith Mason (1893-1973), American soprano, 1929; MS003.001.032.00082 (Box 32)
    - Tamaki Muira (1884-1946), Japanese soprano, 1917; MS003.001.032.00083 (Box 32)
    - Grace Moore (1901-1914), American soprano, 1940; MS003.001.032.00084 (Box 32)
    - Maria Muller (1898-1958), German soprano, 1936; MS003.001.032.00085 (Box 32)
    - Maria Muller (1898-1958), German soprano, 1931; MS003.001.032.00086 (Box 32)
    - Claudia Munzio (1889-1936), Italian soprano, 1922; MS003.001.032.00087 (Box 32)
    - Claudia Munzio (1889-1936), Italian soprano, 1928; MS003.001.032.00088 (Box 32)
    - Alice Nielson (1876-1943), American soprano, 1920; MS003.001.032.00089 (Box 32)
    - Helene (Noldi) AlbertI (1874-1962), soprano, 1950; MS003.001.032.00090 (Box 32)
    - Eida Norena (1884-1968), Norwegian soprano, 1920; MS003.001.032.00091 (Box 32)
    - Adelina Patti (1843-1919), Italian soprano, 1880 -- 1900; MS003.001.032.00092 (Box 32)
    - Mona Paulee (?-1971), American soprano, 1950; MS003.001.032.00093 (Box 32)
    - Frances Peralta (?-1933), soprano, 1900 -- 1940; MS003.001.032.00094 (Box 32)
    - Rose Pauly (1894-1975), Hungarian soprano, 1938; MS003.001.032.00095 (Box 32)
    - May Peterson (1889-1952), American soprano, 1930; MS003.001.032.00096 (Box 32)
    - May Peterson (1889-1952), American soprano, 1930; MS003.001.032.00097 (Box 32)
    - Lily Pons (1904-1976), French soprano, 1925; MS003.001.032.00098 (Box 32)
    - Lily Pons (1904-1976), French soprano, 1935; MS003.001.032.00099 (Box 32)
    - Lily Pons (1904-1976), French soprano, 1940; MS003.001.032.00100 (Box 32)
    - Lily Pons (1904-1976), French soprano, 1935; MS003.001.032.00101 (Box 32)
    - Lily Pons (1904-1976), French soprano, 1935; MS003.001.032.00102 (Box 32)
    - Lily Pons (1904-1976), French soprano, 1945; MS003.001.032.00103 (Box 32)
    - Lily Pons (1904-1976), French soprano, 1950; MS003.001.032.00104 (Box 32)
    - Rosa Ponselle(1897-1981), American soprano, 1923; MS003.001.032.00105 (Box 32)
    - Rosa Ponselle(1897-1981), American soprano, 1927; MS003.001.032.00106 (Box 32)
    - Rosa Ponselle(1897-1981), American soprano, 1936; MS003.001.032.00107 (Box 32)
    - Rosa Raisa (1893-1963), soprano, 1940; MS003.001.032.00108 (Box 32)
    - Marie Rappold (1873-1957), English soprano, 1912; MS003.001.032.00109 (Box 32)
    - Marie Rappold (1873-1957), English soprano, 1900 -- 1920; MS003.001.032.00110 (Box 32)
    - Elizabeth Rethberg (1894-1976), German soprano, 1940; MS003.001.032.00111 (Box 32)
    - Elizabeth Rethberg (1894-1976), German soprano, 1940; MS003.001.032.00112 (Box 32)
    - Elizabeth Rethberg (1894-1976), German soprano, 1930; MS003.001.032.00113 (Box 32)
    - Elizabeth Rethberg (1894-1976), German soprano, 1930; MS003.001.032.00114 (Box 32)
    - Elizabeth Rethberg (1894-1976), German soprano, 1925; MS003.001.032.00115 (Box 32)
    - Marie Hippolyte Roze (1846-1926), French soprano, 1880 -- 1900; MS003.001.032.00116 (Box 32)
    - Gertrude Runger (1899-1965), German soprano, 1950; MS003.001.032.00117 (Box 32)
    - Erma Sack (1903-1972), German soprano, 1945; MS003.001.032.00118 (Box 32)
  - Singers, 8x10s, conductors, mezzo-sopranos, contraltos and sopranos, all signed, 1890 -- 1961; MS003.001.033
    - Kurt Adler (1905-1977), Austrian conductor, 1910 -- 1961; MS003.001.033.00001 (Box 33)
    - Ernest Ansermet (1883-1969), Swiss conductor, 1961; MS003.001.033.00002 (Box 33)
    - Guiseppe Bamboschek (1891-1969), Italian conductor, 1943; MS003.001.033.00003 (Box 33)
    - Sir John Barbirolli (1899-1970), English conductor, 1939; MS003.001.033.00004 (Box 33)
    - Sir John Barbirolli (1899-1970), English conductor, 1939; MS003.001.033.00005 (Box 33)
    - Sir Thomas Beecham (1879-1961), English conductor, 1943; MS003.001.033.00006 (Box 33)
    - Vincenzo Bellezza (1888-1964), Italian conductor, 1936; MS003.001.033.00007 (Box 33)
    - Artur Bedansky (1877-1939), Austrian conductor, 1923; MS003.001.033.00008 (Box 33)
    - Artur Bedansky (1877-1939), Austrian conductor, MS003.001.033.00009 (Box 33)
    - Paul Breisch (1896-1952), Austrian conductor, 1942; MS003.001.033.00010 (Box 33)
    - Fritz Busch (1890-1951), German conductor, 1930; MS003.001.033.00011 (Box 33)
    - Ferruccio Calusio (1891-1983), Argentine conductor, 1941; MS003.001.033.00012 (Box 33)
    - Guido Cantelli (1920-1956), Italian conductor, 1953; MS003.001.033.00013 (Box 33)
    - Andre Caplet (1878-1925), French conposer and conductor, 1913; MS003.001.033.00014 (Box 33)
    - Carlos Chavez (1899-1978), Mexican composer and conductor, 1953; MS003.001.033.00015 (Box 33)
    - Pietro Cimaro (1887-1967), Italian conductor, 1949; MS003.001.033.00016 (Box 33)
    - Fausto Cleva (1902-1971), Italian conductor, 1937; MS003.001.033.00017 (Box 33)
    - Alberta Coates (1882-1953), English conductor, 1923; MS003.001.033.00018 (Box 33)
    - Frank Damrosch (1859-1937), conductor, 1920; MS003.001.033.00019 (Box 33)
    - Walter Damrosch (1862-1950), conductor, 1910 -- 1950; MS003.001.033.00020 (Box 33)
    - Desire Defrere (1888-1964), Belgian baritone, 1940; MS003.001.033.00021 (Box 33)
    - Issay Dobrowen (1894-1953), Russian conductor, 1933; MS003.001.033.00022 (Box 33)
    - Wilhelm Furtwangler (1886-1954), German conductor, 1929; MS003.001.033.00023 (Box 33)
    - Eugene Goosens (1893-1962), English conductor, 1924; MS003.001.033.00024 (Box 33)
    - Herbert Graf (1903-1973), Austrian stage director, 1938; MS003.001.033.00025 (Box 33)
    - Sir Charles Halle (1819-1895), German-English conductor, 1890; MS003.001.033.00026 (Box 33)
    - Henry Hadley (1991-1937), conductor, 1923; MS003.001.033.00027 (Box 33)
    - Richard Hageman (1882-1966), Dutch conductor, 1924; MS003.001.033.00028 (Box 33)
    - Richard Hageman (1882-1966), Dutch conductor, 1937; MS003.001.033.00029 (Box 33)
    - Sir Hamilton Harty (1897-1941), Irish conductor, 1935; MS003.001.033.00030 (Box 33)
    - Louis Hasselmans (1878-1957), French conductor, 1935; MS003.001.033.00031 (Box 33)
    - Alfred Hertz (1872-1942), German conductor, 1923; MS003.001.033.00032 (Box 33)
    - Hans Kindler (1893-1949), Dutch cellist and conductor, 1930; MS003.001.033.00033 (Box 33)
    - Erich Kleiber (1890-1956), Austrian conductor, 1934; MS003.001.033.00034 (Box 33)
    - Otto Klemperer (1885-1973), German conductor, 1936; MS003.001.033.00035 (Box 33)
    - Clemens Krauss (1893-1954), Austrian conductor, 1930; MS003.001.033.00036 (Box 33)
    - Karl Krueger (1894-1979), American conductor, 1937; MS003.001.033.00037 (Box 33)
    - Hans Lange (1884-1960), German conductor, 1937; MS003.001.033.00038 (Box 33)
    - Merle Alcock (1890-1975), American contralto, 1924; MS003.001.033.00039 (Box 33)
    - Elsie Baker (1886-1958), American contralto, 1922; MS003.001.033.00040 (Box 33)
    - Elsie Baker (1886-1958), American contralto, 1956; MS003.001.033.00041 (Box 33)
    - Ina Bourskaya (1888-1954), mezzo-soprano, 1900 -- 1930; MS003.001.033.00042 (Box 33)
    - Karin Branzell (1891-1974), Swedish contralto, 1936; MS003.001.033.00043 (Box 33)
    - Karin Branzell (1891-1974), Swedish contralto, 1951; MS003.001.033.00044 (Box 33)
    - Julia Claussen (1879-1941), Swedish contralto, 1924; MS003.001.033.00045 (Box 33)
    - Sophie Brauzlau (1892-1935), American contralto, 1920; MS003.001.033.00046 (Box 33)
    - Burma Castagna (1905-1983), Italian mezzo-soprano, 1936; MS003.001.033.00047 (Box 33)
    - Burma Castagna (1905-1983), Italian mezzo-soprano, 1936; MS003.001.033.00048 (Box 33)
    - Clara Clemens (1874-1962), American mezzo-soprano, 1900 -- 1930; MS003.001.033.00049 (Box 33)
    - Julia Cup (1880-1970), Dutch contralto, 1910 -- 1930; MS003.001.033.00050 (Box 33)
    - Marguerite D'Alvarez (1886-1953), Peruvian contralto, 1910 -- 1930; MS003.001.033.00051 (Box 33)
    - Maria Gay (1879-1943), Spanish contralto, 1912; MS003.001.033.00052 (Box 33)
    - Maria Gay (1879-1943), Spanish contralto, 1939; MS003.001.033.00053 (Box 33)
    - Maria Gay (1879-1943), Spanish contralto, 1939; MS003.001.033.00054 (Box 33)
    - Jeanne Gordon (1893-1952), Canadian contralto, 1922 -- 1923; MS003.001.033.00055 (Box 33)
    - Jeanne Gordon (1893-1952), Canadian contralto, 1900 -- 1920; MS003.001.033.00056 (Box 33)
    - Louise Homer (1871-1947), American contralto, 1929; MS003.001.033.00057 (Box 33)
    - Louise Homer (1871-1947), American contralto, 1925; MS003.001.033.00058 (Box 33)
    - Kathleen Howard (1880-1956), American contralto, 1925; MS003.001.033.00059 (Box 33)
    - Carolina Lazzari (1891-1946), American contralto, 1930; MS003.001.033.00060 (Box 33)
    - Josephine Jacoby (1875-1948), American contralto, 1947; MS003.001.033.00061 (Box 33)
    - Margaret Matzenauer (1881-1963), Hungarian contralto, 1922; MS003.001.033.00062 (Box 33)
    - Kathryn Meisle (1895-1970), American contralto, 1936; MS003.001.033.00063 (Box 33)
    - Christine Miller, American contralto, 1914; MS003.001.033.00064 (Box 33)
    - Marguerite Namara (1888-1974), American soprano, 1952; MS003.001.033.00065 (Box 33)
    - Marguerite Arndt-Ober (1885-1971), German contralto, 1929; MS003.001.033.00066 (Box 33)
    - Maria Olszewska (1892-1969), German contralto, 1930 -- 1950; MS003.001.033.00067 (Box 33)
    - Sigrid Onegin (1889-1943), German contralto, 1933; MS003.001.033.00068 (Box 33)
    - Carmela Ponselle (1887-1977), American contralto, 1920 -- 1940; MS003.001.033.00069 (Box 33)
    - Ernestine Schumann-Heink (1861-1936), Austrian contralto, 1929; MS003.001.033.00070 (Box 33)
    - Janet Spencer (1874-1948), American contralto, 1910 -- 1940; MS003.001.033.00071 (Box 33)
    - Antoinette Sterling (1850-1904), American contralto, 1890 -- 1900; MS003.001.033.00072 (Box 33)
    - Gladys Swarthout (1904-1969), American mezzo-soprano, 1925 -- 1950; MS003.001.033.00073 (Box 33)
    - Gladys Swarthout (1904-1969), American mezzo-soprano, 1950; MS003.001.033.00074 (Box 33)
    - Gladys Swarthout (1904-1969), American mezzo-soprano, 1930 -- 1960; MS003.001.033.00075 (Box 33)
    - Marguerita Sylva (1875-1957), Belgian soprano, 1900 -- 1920; MS003.001.033.00076 (Box 33)
    - Marguerita Sylva (1875-1957), Belgian soprano, 1924; MS003.001.033.00077 (Box 33)
    - Marguerita Sylva (1875-1957), Belgian soprano, 1925; MS003.001.033.00078 (Box 33)
    - Marion Telva (1897-1962), American contralto, 1930; MS003.001.033.00079 (Box 33)
    - Marion Telva (1898-1962), American mezzo-soprano, 1924; MS003.001.033.00080 (Box 33)
    - Kerstin Thorborg (1896-1970), Swedish contralto, 1940 -- 1960; MS003.001.033.00081 (Box 33)
    - Kerstin Thorborg (1896-1970), Swedish contralto, 1937; MS003.001.033.00082 (Box 33)
    - Jennie Tourel (1910-1973), Russian mezzo-soprano, 1950; MS003.001.033.00083 (Box 33)
    - Cyrena Van Gorden (1896-1964), American contralto, 1920 -- 1940; MS003.001.033.00084 (Box 33)
    - Cyrena Van Gorden (1896-1964), American contralto, 1920 -- 1930; MS003.001.033.00085 (Box 33)
    - Nevada Van der Veer (1884-1958), American contralto, 1930 -- 1950; MS003.001.033.00086 (Box 33)
    - Maria Savage (1865-1957), soprano, 1944; MS003.001.033.00087 (Box 33)
    - Marcella Sembrich (1858-1935), soprano, 1909; MS003.001.033.00088 (Box 33)
    - Franca Somigli (1904-1974), American soprano, 1937; MS003.001.033.00089 (Box 33)
    - Margaret Speaks (1905-1977), American soprano, 1950; MS003.001.033.00090 (Box 33)
    - Adelina Stehle (1865-1945), Italian soprano, 1900 -- 1920; MS003.001.033.00091 (Box 33)
    - Louise Homer Stires (1896-1970), American soprano, 1920; MS003.001.033.00092 (Box 33)
    - Louise Homer Stires (1896-1970), American soprano, 1920; MS003.001.033.00093 (Box 33)
    - Katherine, Louise Sr., and Louise Jr. Homer, American sopranos, 1929; MS003.001.033.00094 (Box 33)
    - Grete Suckgold (1895-1977), German soprano, 1934; MS003.001.033.00095 (Box 33)
    - Maxine Stellman (1906-1972), American soprano, 1940 -- 1950; MS003.001.033.00096 (Box 33)
    - Marie Sundelius (1884-1958), Swedish soprano, 1910 -- 1930; MS003.001.033.00097 (Box 33)
    - Marie Sundelius (1884-1958), Swedish soprano, 1910 -- 1930; MS003.001.033.00098 (Box 33)
    - Milka Ternina (1869-1941), Croatian soprano, 1910; MS003.001.033.00099 (Box 33)
    - Marie Tiffany (?-1948), American soprano, 1922; MS003.001.033.00100 (Box 33)
    - Helen Traubel (1899-1972), American soprano, 1940 -- 1960; MS003.001.033.00101 (Box 33)
    - Elda Vettori (1892-1965), American soprano, 1935; MS003.001.033.00102 (Box 33)
    - Thelma Votipka (1906-1972), American soprano, 1940 -- 1960; MS003.001.033.00103 (Box 33)
    - Carolina White (1886-1961), American soprano, 1917; MS003.001.033.00104 (Box 33)
    - Carolina White (1886-1961), American soprano, 1920; MS003.001.033.00105 (Box 33)
    - Jennette Vreeland (1896-1939), American soprano, 1936; MS003.001.033.00106 (Box 33)
    - Ellen Beach Yaw (1869-1947), American soprano, 1900 -- 1920; MS003.001.033.00107 (Box 33)
  - Singers, 8x10s, tenors, all signed, 1880 -- 1960; MS003.001.034
    - Max Altglass (1895-1952), German tenor, 1940 -- 1950; MS003.001.034.00001 (Box 34)
    - Paul Althouse (1889-1954), American tenor, 1930 -- 1950; MS003.001.034.00002 (Box 34)
    - Paul Althouse (1889-1954), American tenor, 1920 -- 1935; MS003.001.034.00003 (Box 34)